[
    {
        "title" : "Christmas Emojis"
    },


    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "ğŸš—ğŸ¡ğŸ…ğŸ¼",
      "answer": "Driving Home For Christmas"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "ğŸ¥ğŸ‘¦",
        "answer": "Little Drummer Boy"
    },

    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "12xğŸ—“ï¸ğŸ„",
        "answer": "12 Days of Christmas"
      },
      {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "ğŸ™ğŸ¼â„ï¸ğŸ™ğŸ¼â„ï¸",
          "answer": "Let it snow"
      },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "ğŸ‘€ğŸ˜´â„ï¸ğŸ„",
        "answer": "White Christmas"
      },
      {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "ğŸ¶ğŸ””ğŸ¸",
          "answer": "Jingle Bell Rock"
      },

    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "ğŸ‰â¡ï¸ğŸŒ",
        "answer": "Joy to the World"
      },
      {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "â„ï¸â›„ï¸",
          "answer": "Frosty the Snowman"
      },

    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "ğŸ‘ï¸ğŸ‘€ğŸ§â€â™€ï¸ğŸ’‹ğŸ…ğŸ¼",
        "answer": "I saw mummy kissing Santa Claus"
      },
      {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "ğŸ‡ªğŸ‡¸ğŸ˜ğŸ„",
          "answer": "Feliz Navidad"
      }
]
  